Map<String, dynamic> quiz01 = {
  "success": true,
  "message": "quiz 01 data get successfully.",
  "Questions": [
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "23",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "19 + ... = 42",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["23", "22", "21", "24"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "π",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "What is the symbol of Pi?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["π", "€", "Ω", "∞"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "7, 12, 21, 29, 36",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "Arrange the numbers in ascending order: 36, 12, 29, 21, 7",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": [
        "7, 12, 21, 29, 36",
        "7, 12, 29, 21, 36",
        "36, 29, 21, 12, 7 ",
        "None of these"
      ]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "99",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "What is the greatest two digit number?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["99", "11", "10", "90"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "71",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "How much is 90 – 19?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["71", "109", "89", "None of these"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "1",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "20 is divisible by ...",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["1", "None of these", "3", "7"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "17",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "Find the value of x; if x = (2 × 3) + 11",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["17", "55", "192", "66"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "100",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "What is the smallest three digit number?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["100", "999", "111", "101"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "119",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "How much is 190 – 87 + 16?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["119", "103", "261", "87"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "1000",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "What is 1000 × 1 equal to?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["1000", "1", "0", "None of these"]
    }
  ]
};

Map<String, dynamic> quiz02 = {
  "success": true,
  "message": "quiz 02 data get successfully.",
  "Questions": [
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "600",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "In 24,673; the place value of 6 is ...",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "wrong_ans_explanation":
          "Place value of a digit = (face value of the digit) × (value of the place). For example, in the number 475, place value of 5 = 5, place value of 7 = 7 × 10 = 70, and place value of 4 is 4 × 100 = 400.",
      "options": ["600", "6", "10", "100"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "4",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "In 24,673; the face value of 4 is ...",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "wrong_ans_explanation":
          "Face value is the actual value of the digit. For example, in the number 456, the \"5\" has a face value of 5.",
      "options": ["4", "2", "1000", "4000"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "None of these",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "The least number of two digits is ...",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["None of these", "99", "11", "90"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "999,999",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "The largest number of six digits is ...",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["999,999", "100,000", "111,111", "111,000"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "1",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "The smallest number of seven digits is ...",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["1,000,000", "0", "9,999,999", "1,010,100"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "1",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question":
          "The difference between the smallest number of four digits and the largest number of three digits is ...",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["1", "100", "0", "999"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "199",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question":
          "The sum of the least number of three digits and largest number of two digits is ...",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["199", "101", "111", "100"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "2",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question":
          "If a number has an even number or zero at its unit place; the number is always divisible by ...",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["2", "5", "3", "7"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "2",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question":
          "A number is divisible by 3 if the sum of its digits is divisible by ...",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["3", "1", "2", "5"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "0 or 5",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "A number is divisible by 5 if its unit digit is ...",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["0 or 5", "10 or 0", "2 or 0", "None of these"]
    }
  ]
};

Map<String, dynamic> quiz03 = {
  "success": true,
  "message": "quiz 03 data get successfully.",
  "Questions": [
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "666",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "Find the sum of 111 + 222 + 333",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["666", "700", "667", "699"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "375",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "Subtract 457 from 832",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["375", "376", "1289", "275"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "None of these",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "50 times 5 is equal to",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["None of these", "500", "2500", "505"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "9",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "90 ÷ 10 = ...",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["9", "10", "900", "1"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "46",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "26 + 32 - 12 = ...",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["46", "56", "32", "0"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "216",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "Find the product of 72 × 3",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["216", "723", "372", "226"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "176",
      "duration_in_seconds": "45",
      "question": "Solve: 200 – (96 ÷ 4)",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["176", "105", "26", "16"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "25",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "Solve: 24 + 4 ÷ 4",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["25", "6", "28", "7"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "14",
      "duration_in_seconds": "45",
      "question": "Simplify: 3 + 6 x (5 + 4) ÷ 3 - 7",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["14", "15", "16", "11"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "2",
      "duration_in_seconds": "45",
      "question": "Simplify: 150 ÷ (6 + 3 x 8) - 5",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["0", "5", "2", "None of these"]
    }
  ]
};
Map<String, dynamic> quiz04 = {
  "success": true,
  "message": "quiz 04 data get successfully.",
  "Questions": [
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "Four digits",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "How many digits are there in 1000?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["Four digits", "Two digits", "Three digits", "One digit"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "19",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "Complete the sequence 13, 16, ..., 22",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["19", "18", "17", "20"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "97",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "What is the largest two digits prime number?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["97", "96", "98", "99"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "2",
      "duration_in_seconds": "45",
      "question": "How many factors are there in 71?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "wrong_ans_explanation":
          "\"Factors\" are the numbers you multiply to get another number. For instance, factors of 15 are 3 and 5, because 3 × 5 = 15. Factors of 71 are 1 and 71.",
      "options": ["2", "3", "1", "None of these"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "22.5",
      "duration_in_seconds": "45",
      "question": "What is the average value of 25, 20, 23 and 22?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["22.5", "21.5", "20", "24"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "Prime",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "2 is a ... number",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["Prime", "Odd", "Composite", "None of these"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "17",
      "duration_in_seconds": "60",
      "question": "What is the sum of one digit prime numbers?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["17", "15", "13", "11"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "1.5 hours",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "How many hours in 90 minutes?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["1.5 hours", "1.30 hours", "1 hour", "None of these"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "Isosceles triangle",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "Name a triangle whose two angles are equal",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": [
        "Isosceles triangle",
        "Scalene triangle",
        "None of these",
        "Right angle triangle"
      ]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "901",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "4505 ÷ 5 = ...",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["901", "910", "190", "109"]
    }
  ]
};
Map<String, dynamic> quiz05 = {
  "success": true,
  "message": "quiz 05 data get successfully.",
  "Questions": [
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "9004",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "10003 – 999 = ...",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["9004", "4009", "9040", "9400"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "1",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "How many lines can be drawn through two points?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["1", "2", "3", "Not possible"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "None of these",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "Factors of 9 are ...",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["None of these", "1, 6 and 9", "1, 2, 3 and 9", "1, 2 and 3"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "Zero",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question":
          "When we multiply an exact number by zero what will be the exact answer?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": [
        "Zero",
        "The exact number",
        "Cannot be multiplied",
        "None of these"
      ]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "3",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "How many digits answer we will get when we add 99 and 1?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["3", "1", "99", "100"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "99900.0",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "What is 999 times 100.0?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["99900.0", "9990.0", "999.0", "199.0"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "1.01 kg",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "1010 grams = ... kg",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["1.01 kg", "1.001 kg", "101.0 kg", "10.10 kg"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "1000 times",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "How many times 1000 is bigger than 1?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["1000 times", "100 times", "10 times", "1 time"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "27",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question":
          "Average of three person’s age is 9 years. Find the sum of their age.",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["27", "24", "21", "18"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "1 ½ months",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "How many months are equal to 45 days?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["1 ½ months", "1 ¼ months", "¼ months", "2 ¼ months"]
    }
  ]
};
Map<String, dynamic> quiz06 = {
  "success": true,
  "message": "quiz 06 data get successfully.",
  "Questions": [
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "2",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "How many diagonals are there in a quadrilateral?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["2", "3", "4", "No diagonals"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "75 km",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question":
          "Speed of a car is 60 km/hr. Distance covered in 1 ¼ hours is ...",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["75 km", "70 km", "65 km", "60 km"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "1225 m²",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "If one side of a square is 35 m, then the area is ...",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["1225 m²", "1252 m²", "1252 m", "1225 m"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "None of these",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "How many surfaces are there in a cube?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["None of these", "3", "4", "5"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "0.25 kg",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question":
          "How much water is added to 750 g milk to get 1 kilogram mixture of liquid?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["0.25 kg", "2.5 kg", "20.5 kg", "25.0 kg"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "Less than 90 degree",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "An acute angle is ...",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": [
        "Less than 90 degree",
        "90 degree",
        "More than 90 degree",
        "None of these"
      ]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "Meter",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "Which unit is used to measure length and breadth?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["Meter", "Scale", "Liter", "Gram"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "1, 0, and –1",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "What are the integer solutions of the inequality |x| < 2?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["1, 0, and –1", "2, 1, 0, –1, and –2", "2", "2 and –2"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "-6",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "What is the opposite of 6?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["-6", "12", "0", "6"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "-20",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "Which number has the greatest absolute value?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["-20", "0", "-10", "10"]
    }
  ]
};
Map<String, dynamic> quiz07 = {
  "success": true,
  "message": "quiz 07 data get successfully.",
  "Questions": [
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "-4",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "What is –10 – (–6) equals to?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["-4", "4", "-16", "16"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "–14.6, –1.295, 1.07, 24.6, 159",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question":
          "Arrange the following numbers in order from least to greatest; –14.6, 159, 1.07, –1.295, 24.6",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": [
        "–14.6, –1.295, 1.07, 24.6, 159",
        "1.07, –1.295, –14.6, 24.6, 159",
        "1.07, –14.6, 159, 24.6, –1.295",
        "–1.295, –14.6, 1.07, 24.6, 159"
      ]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "3.553",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "Find the sum; –1.54 + 5.093",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["3.553", "–3.553", "–6.63", "6.63"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "-6",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "Which value of x makes the equation true? x – 7 = –13",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["-6", "6", "20", "-20"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "1",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "What is the value of x⁰?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["1", "x", "0", "-1"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "2, 3, 4, 6, 8",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "Which of these following set of numbers are factors of 24?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["2, 3, 4, 6, 8", "1, 5, 12, 18", "4, 7, 24", "3, 9, 12"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "60",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "What is three fifth of 100?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["60", "20", "5", "3"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "19 years",
      "duration_in_seconds": "45",
      "question":
          "If David’s age is 27 years old in 2011. What was his age in 2003?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["19 years", "20 years", "37 years", "17 years"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "None of these",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "What is the remainder of 21 divided by 7?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["None of these", "21", "7", "1"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "0.07",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "What is 7% equal to?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["0.07", "0.007", "0.7", "7"]
    }
  ]
};
Map<String, dynamic> quiz08 = {
  "success": true,
  "message": "quiz 08 data get successfully.",
  "Questions": [
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "77",
      "duration_in_seconds": "45",
      "question":
          "I am a number. I have 7 in the ones place. I am less than 80 but greater than 70. What is my number?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["77", "75", "73", "71"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "225",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "What is the square of 15?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["225", "252", "15", "30"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "13",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "What is the value of x if x² = 169",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["13", "1", "169", "338"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "15/17",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "What is the reciprocal of 17/15?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["15/17", "17/15", "1.13", "30/34"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "1200",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "In a century how many months are there?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["1200", "12", "120", "12000"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "9",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "How many sides are there in a nonagon?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["9", "7", "5", "3"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "None of these",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "Which number occurred before 9019?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["None of these", "9091", "9109", "9099"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "Both odd and prime",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "What kind of number is 37?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["Both odd and prime", "Odd", "Prime", "None of these"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "-1541",
      "duration_in_seconds": "45",
      "question": "13 – 13 × 111 – 111 = ...",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["-1541", "1443", "1319", "1"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "Constant",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "Which term is used to identify a number?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": [
        "Constant",
        "Variable",
        "Both constant and variable",
        "None of these"
      ]
    }
  ]
};
Map<String, dynamic> quiz09 = {
  "success": true,
  "message": "quiz 09 data get successfully.",
  "Questions": [
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer":
          "Parenthesis Exponents Multiplication Division Addition Subtraction",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "What does PEMDAS stand for?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": [
        "Parenthesis Exponents Multiplication Division Addition Subtraction",
        "Parenthesis Even Multiplication Divisor Addition Subtraction",
        "Prime Even Multiple Divisor Add Subtract",
        "None of these"
      ]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "1, 3, 5, 7, 9",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "Which of the following sets are odd numbers?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": [
        "1, 3, 5, 7, 9",
        "2, 3, 7, 9, 11",
        "1, 2, 5, 7, 9",
        "3, 6, 8, 11"
      ]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "14",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "6 – (5 – 3) + 10 = ...",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["14", "17", "21", "27"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "14",
      "duration_in_seconds": "45",
      "question":
          "Find the median of the given data: 13, 16, 12, 14, 19, 12, 14, 13, 14",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "wrong_ans_explanation":
          "To find the median, place the numbers you are given in numerical order and find the middle number.",
      "options": ["14", "12", "14.5", "19"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "1",
      "duration_in_seconds": "45",
      "question": "Simplify: {36 ÷ (-9)} ÷ {(-24) ÷ 6}",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["1", "2", "3", "-1"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "46/7",
      "duration_in_seconds": "45",
      "question": "What should be added to 5 ³/₇ to get 12?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["46/7", "9/34", "2/59", "7/25"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "44 ⁴/₉ m²",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "Each side of a square is 6 ²/₃ m long. Find its area.",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["44 ⁴/₉ m²", "12 ³/₂ m²", "65 ¹/₂ m²", "None of these"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "-25",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "Fill in the blanks: 5/-7 = .../35",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["-25", "25", "5", "30"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "None of these",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "Simplify: 0 × 10²",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["None of these", "10.2", "10", "102"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "5a",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "Subtract -8a from -3a",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["5a", "2a", "-11a", "11a"]
    }
  ]
};
Map<String, dynamic> quiz010 = {
  "success": true,
  "message": "quiz 10 data get successfully.",
  "Questions": [
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "8",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "Solve: x - 3 = 5",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["8", "-8", "-5", "-9"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "60 and 75",
      "duration_in_seconds": "45",
      "question":
          "Two numbers are in ratio 4:5. If the sum of the numbers is 135, find the numbers.",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["60 and 75", "55 and 80", "50 and 85", "65 and 75"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "203 km",
      "duration_in_seconds": "60",
      "question":
          "A car can cover a distance of 522 km on 36 liters of petrol. How far can it travel on 14 liters of petrol?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["203 km", "223 km", "213 km", "302 km"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "11",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question":
          "A long rope has to be cut to make 23 small pieces. If it is double folded to start with how many times does it need to be cut?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["11", "23", "9", "12"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "East",
      "duration_in_seconds": "45",
      "question":
          "A river flows west to east and on the way turns left and go in a semi-circle round a hillock, and then turns left. In what direction is the river finally flowing?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["East", "North", "West", "South"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "8.45",
      "duration_in_seconds": "45",
      "question":
          "A clock seen through a mirror, shows quarter past three. What is the correct time shown by the clock?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["8.45", "3.15", "9.15", "9.45"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "4.00",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question":
          "A clock seen through a mirror shows 8 o'clock. What is the correct time?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["4.00", "8.00", "6.00", "10.00"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "Tuesday, October 25",
      "duration_in_seconds": "60",
      "question":
          "Tom was not at school on Saturday. He was first absent for four days before that. Today is Monday, the 31st of October. When was Tom first absent?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": [
        "Tuesday, October 25",
        "Wednesday, October 26",
        "Monday, October 24",
        "Thursday, October 27"
      ]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "Friday",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "If the day tomorrow is Sunday, what was it yesterday?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["Friday", "Saturday", "Wednesday", "Thursday"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "9900",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "10001 – 101 = ...",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["9900", "9990", "990", "1001"]
    }
  ]
};
Map<String, dynamic> quiz011 = {
  "success": true,
  "message": "quiz 11 data get successfully.",
  "Questions": [
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "31.2",
      "duration_in_seconds": "45",
      "question": "78 ÷ 5 ÷ 0.5 = ?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["31.2", "15.6", "7.8", "20.4"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "30",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question":
          "If ∆ means multiply the first number by second, then (3 ∆ 5) ∆ 2 = ?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["30", "25", "26", "None of these"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "0.09",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "The square root of 0.0081 is ...",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["0.09", "0.9", "0.91", "0.009"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "502",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "What is 1004 divided by 2?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["502", "520", "52", "5002"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "60",
      "duration_in_seconds": "45",
      "question": "Fill in the blanks; 4, 6, 12, 14, 28, 30, ...",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["60", "62", "64", "32"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "10.00",
      "duration_in_seconds": "60",
      "question":
          "Three bells toll at the intervals of 10, 15 and 24 minutes. All the three begin to toll together at 8 o'clock. At what time they will again toll together?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["10.00", "10.45", "9.25", "8.50"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "3 : 5",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "The simplest form of 1.5 : 2.5 is ...",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["3 : 5", "15 : 25", "0.75 : 1.25", "6 : 10"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "237 ½ %",
      "duration_in_seconds": "45",
      "question":
          "Each edge of a cube is increased by 50%. What will be the percent increase in its volume?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["237 ½ %", "133 ¼ %", "150%", "50%"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "25 cm",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question":
          "The diagonals of a rhombus are 30 cm and 40 cm long. Find its side.",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["25 cm", "120 cm", "100 cm", "200 cm"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "1",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "The number which is neither prime nor composite is ...",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["1", "2", "3", "0"]
    }
  ]
};
Map<String, dynamic> quiz012 = {
  "success": true,
  "message": "quiz 12 data get successfully.",
  "Questions": [
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "81",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "Which number is missing? 1, 9, 25, 49, ...",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "wrong_ans_explanation": "It is series of squares of odd numbers.",
      "options": ["81", "121", "16", "169"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "whole",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "Evaluation of 8³ × 8² × 8⁻⁵ is ...",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["1", "0", "8", "None of these"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "0",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "All natural numbers and 0 are called the ... numbers",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["whole", "prime", "integer", "rational"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "2/3",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "Which is the smallest fraction among the following?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["2/3", "6/5", "6/7", "3/4"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "(41, 43, 47)",
      "duration_in_seconds": "60",
      "question":
          "From the alternatives, select the set which is most alike the set (23, 29, 31)",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "wrong_ans_explanation":
          "(23, 29, 37) all are prime numbers. (41, 43, 47) has all prime numbers too.",
      "options": [
        "(41, 43, 47)",
        "(13, 15, 23)",
        "(31, 37, 49)",
        "(17, 21, 29)"
      ]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "7.25",
      "duration_in_seconds": "60",
      "question": "(9321 + 5406 + 1001) ÷ (498 + 929 + 660) = ...",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["7.5", "4.5", "16.5", "3.5"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "12",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "If 6 is 50% of a number, what is the number?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["12", "11", "10", "13"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "36",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question":
          "Area of a parallelogram whose base is 9 cm and height is 4 cm is ... square cm.",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["36", "4", "13", "9"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "20",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question":
          "Andy read 4/5 of a story book which has 100 pages. How many pages of the book is not yet read by Andy?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["20", "40", "60", "80"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "1",
      "duration_in_seconds": "45",
      "question":
          "Which least number should be added to 2600 to make it a perfect square?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "wrong_ans_explanation": "2600+1 is a perfect square (51²=2601)",
      "options": ["1", "3", "5", "39"]
    },
  ]
};
Map<String, dynamic> quiz013 = {
  "success": true,
  "message": "quiz 13 data get successfully.",
  "Questions": [
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": ".83",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "Which of these is the decimal expansion of 5/6?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": [".83", ".16", ".56", "1.2"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "208",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question":
          "What should come in place of question mark in the following question?\n4/13 = 64/?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["208", "198", "168", "228"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "1331",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "What is 121 times 11?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["1331", "1313", "1133", "3131"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "3:4",
      "duration_in_seconds": "90",
      "question":
          "A car covers a distance of 200 km in 2 hours 40 minutes, whereas a jeep covers the same distance in 2 hours. What is the ratio of their speed?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["3:4", "4:3", "4:5", "5:4"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "7",
      "duration_in_seconds": "45",
      "question":
          "A number is greater than 3 but less than 8. Also the number is greater than 6 but less than 10. What is the number?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["7", "6", "8", "5"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "10",
      "duration_in_seconds": "90",
      "question":
          "In the following series a wrong number is given. Find out that number: 4, 5, 10, 18, 34, 59, 95",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "wrong_ans_explanation":
          "The pattern is + 1, + 4, + 9, + 16 (+ 1², + 2², + 3²,+ 4², ...)",
      "options": ["10", "5", "18", "34"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "North-East",
      "duration_in_seconds": "60",
      "question":
          "A clock reads 4:30. If the minute hand points East, in what direction will the hour hand point?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["North-East", "North-West", "North", "South-East"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "5",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "4² + 3² = ...²",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["5", "7", "14", "25"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "81",
      "duration_in_seconds": "45",
      "question": "18/√... = 2",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["81", "36", "18", "6"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "86989",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "90112 – 3123 = ...",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["86989", "87099", "93235", "96989"]
    }
  ]
};
Map<String, dynamic> quiz014 = {
  "success": true,
  "message": "quiz 14 data get successfully.",
  "Questions": [
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "108",
      "duration_in_seconds": "60",
      "question":
          "Which number should come in place of both question marks?\n?/81 = 144/?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["108", "972", "1296", "11664"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "15",
      "duration_in_seconds": "60",
      "question":
          "Which of the following numbers gives 240 when added to its own square?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["15", "16", "18", "20"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "15",
      "duration_in_seconds": "90",
      "question":
          "In a two digit number, the digit in the unit’s place is two more than the three times of the digit in ten’s place. If the sum of the two digits is 6, the number is ...",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["15", "51", "24", "42"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "25%",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "What percentage should be added to 40 to make it 50?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["25%", "15%", "75%", "80%"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "3.12",
      "duration_in_seconds": "30",
      "question": "4.16 × 0.75 = ...",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["3.12", "31.2", "0.0312", "0.312"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "None of these",
      "duration_in_seconds": "90",
      "question":
          "If 5 boys take 7 hours to pack 35 cartoons, then how many boys can pack 65 cartoons in 3 hours?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["None of these", "45", "39", "26"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "\$66",
      "duration_in_seconds": "45",
      "question":
          "You go out for a meal and the total comes to \$55. You want to leave a 20% tip. How much money will you spend total on the meal?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["\$66", "\$75", "\$11", "\$60.50"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "\$5.20",
      "duration_in_seconds": "45",
      "question":
          "\$2496 is spend in the floor repair of 30×16 ft hall. What is repair cost per square feet?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["\$5.20", "\$78.00", "\$12.48", "\$52.00"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "\$768",
      "duration_in_seconds": "90",
      "question":
          "\$600 becomes \$720 in 4 years when the interest is simple. If the rate of interest is increased by 2%, then what will be total amount?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["\$768", "\$725", "\$724", "\$642"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "0",
      "duration_in_seconds": "60",
      "question": "45% of 640 + 64% of 450 = ...% of 1440",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["40", "45", "50", "54"]
    }
  ]
};
Map<String, dynamic> quiz015 = {
  "success": true,
  "message": "quiz 15 data get successfully.",
  "Questions": [
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "734.05",
      "duration_in_seconds": "60",
      "question": "839.093 + 31.005 – 136.048 = ?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["734.05", "734.50", "724.05", "None of these"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "9",
      "duration_in_seconds": "120",
      "question":
          "Take out the wrong number from the given series. 3, 4, 9, 33, 136, 685, 4116",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "wrong_ans_explanation":
          "2nd term = (1st term + 1) * 1, 3rd term = (2nd term + 1) * 2, 4th term = (3rd term + 1) * 3 and so on.",
      "options": ["9", "33", "136", "685"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "20",
      "duration_in_seconds": "120",
      "question": "If 16 = 11, 25 = 12, 36 = 15, then 49 = ?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "wrong_ans_explanation":
          "Formula = first digit + second digit + square root of number.\n16 = 1 + 6 + 4 = 11; 25 = 2 + 5 + 5 = 12;\n36 = 3 + 6 + 6 = 15; 49 = 4 + 9 + 7 = 20",
      "options": ["20", "14", "19", "17"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "156",
      "duration_in_seconds": "120",
      "question":
          "A clock strikes one at 1 o’clock, twice at 2 o’clock, thrice at 3 o’clock and so on. How many times will it strike in 24 hours?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["156", "136", "78", "196"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "2400",
      "duration_in_seconds": "60",
      "question": "106 × 106 – 94 × 94 = ...",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["2400", "2004", "1904", "1906"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "10",
      "duration_in_seconds": "90",
      "question":
          "If '+' means '×', '-' means '+', '×' means '÷' and '÷' means '-' then find the value of:\n6 – 9 + 8 × 3 ÷ 20 = ...",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["10", "-2", "12", "6"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "\$7,040",
      "duration_in_seconds": "90",
      "question":
          "Income of A is 10% more than of B whereas income of B is 20% more than that of C. Income of C is \$2000. What is the sum of incomes of A, B and C?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["\$7,040", "\$7,772", "\$7,046", "\$6,872"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "5x³",
      "duration_in_seconds": "45",
      "question": "What is the sum of 5x³ – 3x² - 1 and 3x² + 1?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["5x³", "6x²", "5x", "3x²"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "11",
      "duration_in_seconds": "45",
      "question": "The cube root of 1331 is ...",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["11", "13", "17", "19"]
    },
    {
      "points": "1",
      "Answer": "\$80",
      "duration_in_seconds": "60",
      "question":
          "The wages of 10 workers for a six-day week is \$1200. What are the one day’s wages of 4 workers?",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question_type": "1",
      "options": ["\$80", "\$32", "\$24", "\$40"]
    }
  ]
};
